(Sheldon:)Remember how Leonard told you
we couldn't come...
(Sheldon:)...because we were attending a symposium
on molecular positronium?
(Penny:)I remember symposium.
(Sheldon:)Yes, well, he lied.
(Penny:)Wait, what?
(Sheldon:)He lied, and I'm feeling
very uncomfortable about it.
(Penny:)Well, imagine how I'm feeling.
(Sheldon:)Hungry?
(Sheldon:)Tired?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, this really isn't my strong suit.
You told her I lied?
(Leonard:)Why would you tell her I lied?
(Sheldon:)To help you.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, I'm not seeing the help.
(Sheldon:)She was going to see
through your lie eventually...
(Sheldon:)...so I told her that you were lying
to protect me.
[LEONARD GROANS]
(Leonard:)Oh, I'm getting a bad feeling.
(Sheldon:)Hunger?
Indigestion?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry,
I'm really not very good at this.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, Penny now believes
that on Friday night...
(Sheldon:)...we're going to participate
in my cousin Leopold's drug intervention.